That a very long term
chart of ICICI Lombard General
Insurance Company is presented before you, you will be
seen discussing its results, Ash,
good morning, look at this,
this quarter of the last quarter has been a bit soft,
weak figures have been presented, actually here
due to better performance the underwriting office has
increased a lot and
due to this the pressure on profitability has worsened,
see it has come down from 398 crores to 152 crores,
against the profit of 38 crores, the
underwriting loss has come to 508 crores
in this quarter, that is why we have seen that
fresh ginger sir,
next PM not, look at the profit figures, there
is definitely a slight increase in it, you have seen this loss of around 276 crores,
but that figure has been more
heavy, we have seen in the earnings figures
also, the figure has increased by 102 percent to
121 crores, but there has been
disappointment in the cost, actually these condolences
are more in this quarter, here today
in the same quarter last year it was 1621 crores,
this time it appeared to be 2468 crores
And because of this,
hello hello, the underwriting has increased and the
pressure is on the plate,
where so what to see, such people, the rest of the
numbers for as it comes, the machine
seems to be a little weak, number six,
who is the enemy of the user's problem, you should
definitely put it on the number of, okay,
I have got a report from someone from below,
they said that there is definitely a Taliban of
scooter, that is why they have definitely made a
revision in Tigers, but it is
not very big, the first target was 1575 rupees, after
revising it, tests have been done around 1600 rupees
and the
rating is of the outperform side, they believe that the
situation in the second half and share will be
seen happening a little, due to this,
in the quarterly comparison, on the other hand, in the fourth quarter
guest house, there will be more
special inside, underwriting and
numbers of mute bandits of around ₹500 will be learned,
but yes, they feel that the overall
situation will have to be 1423 on words as soon as it becomes better, the
replacement for f22 will definitely be
removed, cars paste percent  But
for Refer 2334, only around three to five
percent of the patient data is
showing a lot of damage overall but yes,
still Tiger Shroff's rating is there on the Appoint site,
so let us present to you this strategy that brokers are
setting.